[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "You say he seems laid back, is that what you said?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, no, no one was giving me any information.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Can you do it without the earpiece in?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "You know you don't worry about the negativity.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "You know, obviously we're not running for president so our positions don't really matter.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Are you completely wedded and fined up to these positions that the party takes?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "I think my dad's been very compassionate in his views.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Do you wish sometimes that the language used by the Republicans was less emotive?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, in a view brief sentences, I guess, for me, at least, it's taught me great values in my life, how to live my life, how to treat other people, just like a lot of faiths that are out there that are a lot of great things about Mormonism, how to -- you know, how to live your life and treat your neighbor and love others.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "What are the great assets of being a Mormon, that you would advocate?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "These are all things that have been great blessings in my life at least.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Do you ever feel like, damn it, I wish we hadn't been Mormons?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "You know, I hope so.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Craig, this time with you, do you think actually it's a great asset?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "You know, as Tagg pointed out earlier, this is the game of politics and we're prepared for that.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "When you get people attacking him for his success and his wealth?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Knowing your father as you do, can you guarantee to the American people he's got nothing to hide about his finances?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Frugal.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Ben?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Qualified.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Frugal?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I've done that many times.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "If you were going to tear down the president, how would you do it?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "When it comes to the president, do you think he's an honest man?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, listen, I think he misleads people in political commercials.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "You don't think he misleads the American public?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "I think on certain areas of education policy I agree with him, trying to empower charter schools and choice around the country.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Has he been dead wrong about everything or can you find things to credit him with?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "I mean, this is a man with an extraordinarily good heart.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "What are the qualities that maybe we're not aware of?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I hope he does, because if he does, the American people are going to like him and trust him and make him the next president of the United States.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Is Thursday the time for him to sort of metaphorically rip open his jacket and say, this is the real Mitt?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "First of all, the statistic that it's the highest in 35 years is wrong.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "HRISTIE: The fact of the matter is that the national economy has a huge effect on what happens in New Jersey.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Who do you blame, yourself or Barack Obama, for unemployment in New Jersey?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Listen, since last October, I've traveled to 15 different states for Mitt Romney.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Did you have literally no aspirations to be leader of the free world?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "And I'd say there's two factors to this.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Is he a guy who can relate to the ordinary Americans in the street?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I happened -- again, I may be an aberration, but I think his wealth was earned.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "It's one the problems, transparency here, that people know he's very rich and there are ongoing concerns about exactly why he got to be so rich?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "It's possible, sure.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Is it possible to get this deficit significantly reduced from $16 trillion without some tax increase?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "CCAIN: I think he's in pretty good shape.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "What is your take on it?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "I'm sorry for that.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "As a Republican, how do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I'm very well, thank you.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Dr. Rice, how are you?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Well, look, there was great pride -- and I shared it -- in America's first black president.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "At the moment, there's a perception that Mitt Romney's decided, you know, Barack Obama, I can't beat him with the black vote, so there's no point wasting time and energy chasing a vote I'm not going to get?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "No, I really didn't want that.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "You really didn't want that?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Piers, I wrote a memoir called \"No Higher Honor.\"", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Are you 100 percent or 99.99?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "No, but I'm working on it.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Have you chosen your first partner to play with you?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Well, I banned myself until they allowed women back, so I've now released my own ban.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "You ready?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Well, what has happened is a dramatic expansion of government entitlement programs and programs like -- and more to come, Obamacare, which is a huge government expansion that is going to, quote, \"guarantee people health insurance,\" which of course, you know, it does not necessarily mean health care.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "That is not what has happened, is it?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Well, I would make the argument that when you dramatically expand the size and scale of government, when you dramatically expand social welfare programs, when you provide waivers to work requirements, as he did -- people don't talk about this, but two years ago, he did a waiver to Food Stamp's work requirement, and Food Stamps have exploded.", "docId": "120831pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Why go after things which just don't really stack up?", "qSentId": 597}]